Finding Aid for United States Army Signal Corps photograph collection 1918-1919
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Print Nos. 152821-152839, 12 prints (Folder 6)
    - Print No. 152823 January 8, 1919 (Item 3)
      (A snow covered dugout, at a point on the high ground overlooking the Padenga river. It is equipped with one Vikers and one Lewis machine gun. A non-commissioned officer and two Vikers, men, two Lewis men, and six privates are on duty in the dugout. In the picture from left to right are: Sgt. F.W. Yates, Co. A, 310th Engrs.; Pvt. Mike Christy; Pvt. Leo Peters; and Corpl. William J. Lehman; all of Co. A,339th Infantry. Vysokaya Gora, Ust Padenga Front, Vaga River Column, Russia.)
    - Print No. 152824 January 8, 1919 (Item 4)
      (An 18 pounder 3.3 gun manned by the center section 68th Battalion Canadian Field Artillery, outside the log shelter, which has been built to protect the gun from the extremely low temperatures. Two such field guns are used in the defense of the positions at the Ust Padenga Front. To the left of the picture is Lt. J.D. Winskow, who commands this battery of Canadian field artillery. Vysokaya Gora, Ust Padenga Front, Vaga River Column, Russia.)
    - Print No. 152825 January 8, 1919 (Item 5)
      (A picture taken with a twenty four inch lens, of the village of Pagosta, from an American outpost overlooking the Pagenda valley. In the village of Pagosta is the outpost of the enemy. A machine gun mounted in the middle belfry of the church opens fire almost daily on the outpost from which this picture was secured. Early on the morning that his picture was taken a Bolshevik patrol attempted to reach this American outpost, but were discovered. One was killed and the others fled. Vysokaya Gora, Ust Padenga Front Vaga River Column, Russia.)
    - Print No. 152826 January 8, 1919 (Item 6)
      (Here are shown the American and British officers in command of the forces at the Vaga river front. This front is the most distant of all from the base at Archangel, approximately 400 versts. In the front row, right to left are: Lieut. J. Douglas Winslow, 68th Battery, C.F.A.; Capt. O.A. 0djard, Co. A, 339th Inf. officer in command, Ust Padenga front; 1st Lieut. Harry H. Mead, Co. A. 339th Inf.; 1st Lieut. A.F. Collar, Co. A, 339th Inf., Second row, right to left; 2nd Lt. H.D. McPhaie, Co. A, 339th Inf; Lieut. A.M. McMurray, F.E.; 2nd Lt. V.A. Burns, Co. A, 310th Engrs.; 1st Lt. Edward J. Sarry, Co. A, 339th Infantry. Vysokaya, Gora, Ust Padenga Front, Vaga River Column, Russia.)
    - Print No. 152827 January 8, January 8, 1919 (Item 7)
      (Russian peasant's home at the Ust Padenga front, occupied by a detachment of the 337th Field Ambulance Co. Some of the men in the detachment are in the foreground, while Lt. R. Powers the officer in charge is seated on the sled. Note: 1st Lt. R. Powers has been killed since the date when this picture was taken, during a Bolshevik attack on the American positions at Ust, Padenga, Vysokaya Gora, Ust Padenga front, Vaga river column, Russia.)
    - Print No. 152829 January 10, 1919 (Item 8)
      (Although rather out of season baseball is played daily by the men of Company B, 339th Inf. stationed at Kitsa. An indoor baseball outfit is used; making it possible to play in the snow. Kitsa, Russia. (Village on the line of communications between Berezniki, and Shenkhurst))
    - Print No. 152834 January 16, 1919 (Item 9)
      (American officers and men with expert Frenchmen as their tutors are rapidly becoming skilled in the sport of skiing. Daily practice is held along the banks of the Emetsi river and in picture some of the officers and men are shown engaged in the sport. Leading is 1st Lieut. J.G. Streng, followed by 2nd Lt. Wallace Templeton, both of Company F, 339th Infantry, Emetskoe, Russia.)
    - Print No. 152835 January 16 1919 (Item 10)
      (The busy market place, in Emetskoe viewed from the belfry of the church about which the peasants display their goods. There is one market day a week, Thursday. Emetskoe, Russia.)
    - Print No. 152837 January 18, 1919 (Item 11)
      (A Rusky driver, dressed in a heavy coat of reindeer skin for protection against the severe cold, setting out with his loaded sled which is typical of the kind employed in all overland transportation in northern Russia. Jillena, Russia. (rest stop between Archangel and Berezniki))
    - Print No. 152839 January 18, 1919 (Item 12)
      (A convoy winding its way along a forest road. The rolling character of the ground, the twisting of the road, the clearing through the forests on each side of the road, all of which are typical of miles and miles of roads in northern Russia, are illustrated in this picture. This was taken early in the afternoon at the start of a journey of nineteen versts. In a distance forty four versts only one log cabin was seen, and that was the rest house, where the convoy rested five hours before proceeding. Jillena, Russia. (Rest stop between Archangel and Berezniki))
  - Print Nos. 156848-158889, 23 prints (Folder 7)
    - Print No. 156848 April 2, 1919. (Item 1)
      (American officers gathered in front of the Headquarters of the American North Russian Expeditionary Forces in Archangel, Front row, L to. R: Capt. James R. Fitzsimmons, Co. "C" 339th Inf.; Capt. Wm. Knight; 310th Eng.; Col George E. Stewart, Commanding Officer, 339th Inf.; Lt. Col. Edward Thurston, Judge Advocate; Major Jonas R. Longley, 337th Field Hospital.; Major William H. Henry, Medical Detachment, 310th Engrs.; Major John C. Hall, Med. Detch. 339th Inf.; Major Malcolm Douglas, Med. Detch. 339th Inf. Back row, L to R.: Lt. Chas. E. Lewis, Asst, Adjutant 339th Inf.; Chaplain John S. Landowski, Lt. William L. Jones, Med. Detch. 339th Inf.; Captain Harry E. Carrier, Personnel Adjutant, 339th Inf.; Lt. Roy Brieger, Statistical Officer, Lt. Verne W. McClung, Co. "E", 339th Inf.; Capt, Alex M. Lowenstein, 339th Field Hosp.; Capt. Howard W. Geiger; Med. Detch, 339th Inf.; 2nd Lt. John E. Brown, Supply Co. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158850 April 2, 1919 (Item 2)
      (Capt. O.D. Odjard, Commanding Officer Co, 'W', 339th Inf. 85th Div, who has been decorated with the Military Cross for bravery in action. Owing to a shrapnel wound in the neck, Capt. Odjard has been evacuated to the United States, Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158851 April 5, 1919 (Item 3)
      (Capt. Joel Moore, Co. M, 339th Inf. 85th Div, displaying a sword which formerly belonged to a Battalion Commander of the 6th Saratov Regiment, who was killed during an engagement between Bolshevik forces and Co. "M" near Bolshie Ozerka, Capt. Moore is surrounded by men of his company Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158852 April 5, 1919 (Item 4)
      (Officers of Co. "M", 339th Inf. 85th Div. Immediately after the return of the company from Bolshie Ozerka front where they repulsed repeated Bolshevik attacks. From L. to R: Lt. Clarence J. Primm, 2nd Lt. Milton J. Carpenter, 2nd Lt. Weiszorek, Lt. Wesley K. Wright, Lt. James R. Donovan, Lt. George M. Stoner, and Capt. Joel Moore. Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - 158854 April 7, 1919 (Item 5)
      (Aeroplane, piloted by Russian, seen over the roofs of the log houses in Obozerskaya, returning to aeroplane after a flight over enemy lines. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158857 Russia April 8, 1919 (Item 6)
      (An American Engineer Pvt. Charles Mock, Co. "C", 310th Engrs. Standing guard behind a hurriedly constructed barricade of logs at Verst-18, 339th Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Oaerka Front.)
    - Print No. 158861 April 8, 1919 (Item 7)
      (Blockhouse No. 1, the most advanced allied position along the road in the direction of Bolshie Ozerka. The blockhouse and clearing surrounding it were made by men of the 3rd Platoon Co. Co. C, 310 Eng. 339 Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front. Russia.)
    - Print No. 158863 April 8, 1919 (Item 8)
      (Convoy of empty sleds, driven by Russian soldiers returning to Obozerskaya for a fresh supply of ammunition and food for the allied forces fighting in the vicinity of Bolshie Ozerka. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158864 April 8, 1919 (Item 9)
      (Bridge across a marsh on the allied line of communications between Obozerskaya and the Bolshie Ozerka Front. Allied secondary defence positions for the protection of Obozerskaya were being constructed on the opposite bank of the marsh. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158865 April 8, 1919 (Item 10)
      (Convoy of sleds moving along the forest trail between Obozerskaya and the Bolshie Ozerka Front. 339th Inf. 85th. Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158867 April 8, 1919 (Item 11)
      (Bolshevik soldier, one of a number killed in an attempted flank attack on the positions held by allied troops on the Obozerskaya road at Verst 16, 339th Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158869 April 8, 1919 (Item 12)
      (Another snap showing shell fire by Russian artillery bursting in the vicinity of Bolshevik outposts. Picture taken from post at Verst 18, 339th Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front, Russian)
    - Print No. 158870 April 8, 1919 (Item 13)
      (Russian artillery in position along the road to Bolshie Ozerka at Verst 16. This artillery kept up a continuous fire against the village and hastened the withdrawl of the Bolshevik forces which temporarily held that point. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158871 April 8, 1919 (Item 14)
      (Russian Red Cross at work, a Russian soldier administering first aid to an injured comrade near Bolshie Ozerka front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158873 April 8, 1919 (Item 15)
      (Men from 3rd Platoon, Co. "C" 310th Engrs. grouped outside their tent near the Bolshie Ozerka Front. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 150874 April 8, 1919 (Item 16)
      (Tents of Co. "C" 310th Engrs. pitched among forest trees at the side of the road. Verst 18, 339th Inf. 85th Div. Bolshie Ozerka Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158877 April 9, 1919 (Item 17)
      (Trench leading through the deep snow to an outpost at Verst 444. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Vologda Railway Front. Russia.)
    - Print No. 158878 April 9, 1919 (Item 18)
      (Col. George E. Stewart, 339th Info 85th Div. at the Vologda Railway front, examining a list of Allied prisoners held by the Bolsheviks, which was brought back by American officers after a parley in No Man's Land with Bolshevik officers concerning the exchange of prisoners. L to R: Lt. Gordon Reese, Co. "I", 339th Inf.; Lt. Dwight Fistler, Co. "I", 339th Inf.; Col. George E. Stewart, C.O. 339th Inf.; Major Brooks Nichols, 3rd Bn. 339th Inf.; Capt. Horatio Winslow, Co. "I", 339th Inf. Vologda Railway Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158880 April 9, 1919 (Item 19)
      (Col. George E. Stewart, Commanding Officer, 339th Info and Major J. Brooks Nichols, 339th Info inspecting a trench mortar belonging to the trench mortar platoon hdqrs. Co. in position at Verst 444. At the right if Lt. Charles I. R. Reid, Photographic Unit, 339th Inf. 85th Div.Vologda Railway Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158882 April 9, 1919 (Item 20)
      (Dugout among the wood piles in the clearing at Verst 444 where men of the trench mortar platoon hdqrs. co. are quartered, when not actually on duty. Enemy shell fire has destroyed all the building above ground in the clearing. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Vologda Railway Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158883 April 9, 1919 (Item 21)
      (Men of Machine Gun Co. 339th Inf. 85th Div. sawing and preparing logs to be used in the construction of a dugout adjoining the blockhouse which stands at the left of the Vologda Railway Line at Verst 445 1/2 Vologda Railway Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 158887 April 9, 1919 (Item 22)
      (Six inch, long range, naval gun mounted on a steel coal car Verst 455 This gun which is manned by an all Russian naval gun crew, is used to shell the Bolshevik Base at Yemtsa. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Vologda Railway Front Russia.)
    - Print No. 158889 April 9, 1919 (Item 23)
      (Naval gun and gun crew preparing to load the 6 inch naval gun used on the Vologda railway front. When firing the gun is run up from its base at Verst 455. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Vologda Railway Front, Russia.)
  - Print Nos. 159489-161113, 4 prints (Folder 8)
    - Print No. 159489 April 17, 1919 (Item 1)
      (Brig. Gen. W. P. Richardson about to cross the Dwina by reindeer team. Gen. Richardson arrived in Archangel shortly before the last of the few remaining Laplanders drove their reindeer teams northward. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 159506 May 15, 1919 (Item 2)
      (Officers mess headquarters, 339th Inf. showing in order from L to R: Major William H. Henry, Med. Det. 310th Engrs.; Col. Geo. E. Stewart, C.O. 339th Inf.; Capt. M. A. Gaff, Adj. 339th Inf.; Lt. Col. Edward S. Thurston, Judge Advocate-2nd Row -- Lt. Col. Erastus Corning, Chief Surgeon, Maj. James R. Longley, 337th Field Hospital, Maj. John C. Hall, 339th Med. Det.; Maj. Malcolm Douglass, 339th Med. Det.; 2nd Lt. Roy Bricker, Personnel Adj. (Brigade), Capt. Howard W. Geiger, 339th Med. Det., Capt. H. E. Carrier, Personnel Adj. 339th Inf., 1st Lt. R. L. Jerry, Tank Corps, at the end of table, 1st Lt. Charles I, Reid, Photo Unit, Signal Corps, 4th Row -- 1st Lt. Will L. Jones, D.C. 339th Med. Det., 1st Lt. John C. Kiley, 337th Amb. Co.; 2nd Lt. Tom Devine, Intelligence officer, Brig. Hdqrs, 5th Row- 1st Lt. Henry Katz, 339th Med. Det., Capt. Joseph Rosenfeld, 337th Amb. Co.; 2nd Lt. R.R. Chatterton, Q.M.C., Capt. Clarence A. Greenleaf, 339th Med. Det., (at end of table) 1st Lt. Charles E. Lewis, Asst. Adj. 339th Inf. 6th row- 2nd Lt. John Brown, Supply Co., 339th Inf; 1st Lt. Forest J. Funk, S.C. attached, Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161107 February 19, 1919 (Item 3)
      (Major J. Brooks Nicholas, 3rd Bn. 339th Inf. 85th Div. and officer commanding Vologda Railway Detachment at work in his office which is established in a box car at Verst 455. With the desk at one end, sleeping accommodations are provided at the other end of the car. Verst 455, Vologda R. R. Front, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161113 February 21, 1919 (Item 4)
      (American soldiers on patrol wearing white capes to reduce the chance of discovery while operating in the snow blanketed forests which line the Vologda R.R. line on each side. The picture shows the character of the forest in which the American forces live and fight. Left to right Buglar Chas, Metcalf. Co. I.; Pvt. Harold Holliday, Co. M. and Sgt. Maj. Ernest Reed, 3rd Bn. 339th Inf. 85" Div. Verst 455 Vologda R.R. Front, Russia.)
  - Print Nos. 161680-161697, 14 prints (Folder 9)
    - Print No. 161680 February 27, 1919 (Item 1)
      (Funeral of Wagoner James E. Byles, Supply Co. 339th Inf. 85th Div. casket covered by an American flag being lowered into the grave. Chaplain John S. Landowski, who was in charge of the service is shown in the picture. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161683 March 4, 1919 (Item 2)
      (Laplanders with their reindeer team waiting for passengers at Archangel Prestin. A regular taxi service is carried on in this manner, The fare from Archangel Prestin being three roubles (30 cents). The distance is about one mile. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161684 March 6, 1919 (Item 3)
      (Picture taken to show an aeroplane fitted with skis, the depth of the snow and the conditions encountered having rendered the use of machines impossible except when equipped in this manner. The machine is a Sopwith belonging to the Royal Air Force. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161685 March 6, 1919 (Item 4)
      (A Sopwith aeroplane equipped with skis leaving a newly constructed airdrome at Archangel for Beresniki. The Pilot is 1st Lt. Gergeii Shebelin of the Slavo-British Air Force, formerly a Col. in the Russian Imperial Infantry. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161687 March 7, 1919 (Item 5)
      (A Lapp driver and his reindeer team. While waiting for business the old man smokes away contentedly at his pipe. This picture shows the type of light but strong wooden sleds employed by the Laplanders as well as the rope harness by which the reindeer are attached to the sled, and the long pole or gaff, which takes the place of a whip. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 181688 March 7, 1919 (Item 6)
      (American officers frequently employ reindeer teams in crossing the Dwina River and in going from point to point about Archangel. Here are shown two officers of the Q.M. Corps, Major E. F. Ely and 2nd Lt. R.R. Chatterton, (at the left) with a team which they have just engaged to take them to Archangel Prestin. A Russian young lady (barishna) is also a passenger. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161689 March 7, 1919 (Item 7)
      (A lap girl in her brightly decorated robe or reindeed skin with three reindeed which form a part of the team which she drives. A large number of women from Lapland accompany the men on their journeys to Archangel from the frozen tundra, 339th Inf. 58th Div. Archangel Russia.)
    - Print No. 161690 March 7, 1919 (Item 8)
      (A Lapp with his reindeed setting out from the north shore of the Dwina River with French and American soldiers as passengers. A typical wild Russian dog is shown in this picture. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel Russia.)
    - Print No. 161691 March 7, 1919 (Item 9)
      (Reindeer teams. In the background of one of the churches of Archangel 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel Russia.)
    - Print No. 161693 March 7, 1919 (Item 10)
      (Lapps counting over their receipts in roubles for the day. Three, roubles, thirty cents in American money is the charge for a trip across the Dwina River. Many trips can be made back and forth during an afternoon and the receipts often run high. 339th Inf. 85th. Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161694 March 8, 1919 (Item 11)
      (A woman from Lagland with her reindeed team waiting for passengers who wish to cross the river. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel Russia.)
    - Print No. 161695 March 8, 1919 (Item 12)
      (Hospital ship. Kalyan (British) which wintered in Archangel. The picture shows the ship fast in the thick ice of the Dwina River. American sick and wounded coming back from the front are sometimes cared for on board this ship. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel Russia.)
    - Print No. 161696 March 8, 1919 (Item 13)
      (Two American soldiers of Hq. Co., anticipating their return home hunt about the market place in Archangel for souvenirs. 339th Inf. 85th. Div. Archangel Russia.)
    - Print No. 161697 March 8, 1919 (Item 14)
      (A Russian sled silhouetted against the setting sun on its way across the Dwina River. This is one of the types of sleighs frequently used along the lines of communication. 339th Inf. 85th. Div. Archangel Russia.)
  - Print Nos. 161701-161725, 8 prints (Folder 10)
    - Print No. 161701 March 14, 1919 (Item 1)
      (A battery of Russian Field Artillery drawn up on the Dwina River for practice maneuvers, This battery, along with others, which have been trained by French Officers, will soon take its place at one of the fronts. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel. Russia.)
    - Print No. 161702 March 14, 1919 (Item 2)
      (Russian Field Artillery moving out across the Dwina River. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel. Russia.)
    - Print No. 161704 March 14, 1919 (Item 3)
      (The transportation of people across the Dwina River from Archangel to Archangel Prestin where the Vologda Railway ends, a distance of slightly more than a mile, is accomplished in various ways, but chiefly by reindeer teams, consisting of from two to five animals each. A dark skinned Laplander is the driver and the passengers ride on a light wooden sled over which a deer skin is thrown, here one of these is crossing the river. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161705 March 14, 1919 (Item 4)
      (A reindeer team crossing the Dwina. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161706 March 14, 1919 (Item 5)
      (Russians carrying sacred banner, crosses and ikons, in one of the religious processions which are frequently seen on the streets of Archangel. This procession, which set out early in the morning marched about the whole city from church to church until late afternoon. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161707 March 16, 1919 (Item 6)
      (American soldiers coasting down the slide or gorka constructed on one of the down town streets of Archangel by American Engineers. An icy runway leads out into the river a distance of a quarter of a mile. 339" Inf. 85th. Div., Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 161724 March 28, 1919 (Item 7)
      (Co. I. minstrels at the Y.M.C.A. in Archangel. Two performances were given before an audience which packed the hall. 339th Inf. 85" Div. Archangel Russia.)
    - Print No. 161725 March 29, 1919 (Item 8)
      (American, English and French officers with Russian officers and friends, attending a moving picture show and dance at American Hdqrs. 339th Inf. 85th Div. Archangel Russia.)
  - Oversize prints, 41 prints (Folder 11)
    - Print No. 28596 September 28, 1918 (Item 1)
      (Small detachment of French troops waiting to move to the front two days before the attack made by the Allied forces, in attempt to drive the enemy forces south along the railroad to the Vologda. Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - Print No. 28602 September 6, 1918 (Item 2)
    - Print No. 28608 September 18, 1918 (Item 3)
      (Casket of Lieut. Marchs T. Casey covered with American flag, being lowered into grave. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 32053 September 21, 1918 (Item 4)
    - Print No. 32061 September 28, 1918 (Item 5)
      (French troops gathering, preliminary to attack on the Bolsheviks. Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - Print No. 32062 September 21, 1918 (Item 6)
      (Pumping station blown up by the Bolsheviks. Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - Print No. 32063 September 21, 1918 (Item 7)
      (View of Obozerskaya, now occupied by the Allied troops, serving as an advanced base for operation at the front. Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - Print No. 32068 September 24, 1918 (Item 8)
      (Mortar being fired from armored car. Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - Print No. 32075 September 27, 1918 (Item 9)
    - Print No. 36750 (Item 10)
      [no Signal Corps description provided]
    - Print No. 39243 September 6, 1918 (Item 11)
    - Print No. 39244 September 13, 1918 (Item 12)
      (Members of 339th Regiment Infantry in front of Headquarters. Archangel, Russia.)
    - Print No. 40589 November 15, 1918 (Item 13)
      (Barracks erected by Company of the 310th Engrs. The building is located immediately in the rear of the railroad station. The southeast corner of the structure is shown in the picture. Obozerskaya, Russia.)
    - Print No. 40600 November 16, 1918 (Item 14)
      (Allies at the front joyriding on an old Russian engine. Verst 455, Russia.)
    - Print No. 40603 November 16, 1918 (Item 15)
      (First blockhouse on the left band side of track (looking southeast) Verst 465, Russia.)
    - Print No. 79448 (Item 16)
    - Print No. 79449, na 16,997 (Item 17)
    - Print No. 79450 (Item 18)
    - Print No. 79458 (Item 19)
    - Print No. 79460 (Item 20)
    - Print No. 79461, na 16,998 (Item 21)
    - Print No. 79462 (Item 22)
    - Print No. 79466 (Item 23)
    - Print No. 79469 (Item 24)
    - Print No. 152740 (Item 25)
    - Print No. 152783 December 21, 1918 (Item 26)
    - Print No. 152822 (Item 27)
    - Print No. 157788 (Item 28)
    - Print No. 158849 April 8, 1919 (Item 29)